- What happened to Serizawa?
- He's sick.
I want to meet him.
Suzuki.
You really came.
You've never felt your heart beat faster
when you're around Serizawa?
Maybe I...
Sorry, I'm going home!
Don't go.
Maybe...
I really do like Serizawa.
Serizawa?
Wait!
Can I kiss you?
What are you...
Suzuki.
You like me, don't you?
Hey, wait!
No...
Don't!
A dream?
For real? Oh no...
My imagination is running wild...
Yesterday night...
My heart was beating like crazy, so...
Sorry, change of plans.
I'm going home.
- Huh?
- I'm really sorry!
Call or text if you need something.
Take care!
Maybe...
I do like Serizawa.
[Notification]
Morning, Suzuki! Thanks for coming yesterday.
Your nursing put me right back in gear.
And you felt great as a body pillow.
What?
I take back everything I thought earlier.
I won't fall in love with Serizawa.
[Quit teasing me]
[Episode 5]
Morning.
- Hey.
- 'Sup.
What's going on?
Well...
Serizawa's being held prisoner.
By who?
Some third year upperclassmen.
Take a look.
- Why not?
- Sorry.
I made plans to play ball with the boys.
- Let us join you!
- Or ditch them!
Did Serizawa get on their bad side?
Far from it.
A date?
Remember those snacks we had the other day?
Snacks...
Koha got them from her upperclassmen.
For real? Sweet!
- Right.
- Yeah, well those snacks
were a trap.
A trap?
They asked Serizawa out on a date
in exchange for those snacks.
Huh?
It's not a date.
One of the girls just wants to hang out
and chat for an hour after school.
We call that a date.
If you're not up for it, tell her no.
I did.
But her friends pressured me like crazy.
They insisted it'd only be the one time.
Dude, why are you so upset? It's a date.
If anything,
you could take her as your girlfriend.
I'm not really a fan of dating for fun.
I don't want to hurt my partners,
knowing my heart's not in it 100%.
That's why all your relationships
have failed.
Suzuki, did I disappoint?
No, not at all.
So, does that mean you...
Uh...
You don't have a girlfriend now?
- Yeah.
- You just realized?
Sorry.
I didn't know.
I'm single.
Have been for over a year now.
I see.
That's unexpected.
I'm the only taken dude here.
Wait, really?
Yeah. I'm not looking to date right now.
And I don't need a girlfriend.
Yeah, 'cause you prefer playing around.
- Ouch.
- I see.
My bad.
What about you, Suzuki?
Me?
I don't have anyone like that.
Romance is far beyond me anyway.
You've never dated anyone?
Nope.
I see.
So, when's your date
with the upperclassman?
We haven't decided. And it's not a date!
Who knows? Maybe you two will get along.
- It's a date!
- It's not!
A date! A date!
[Date]
A date.
Right.
I'm sure the girls must love Serizawa.
They'd get into the mood,
feel that special pull,
and maybe start dating right then and there?
Suzuki.
Serizawa.
I knew I'd find you here.
Were you writing?
Yeah.
Everything okay?
Huh? Why?
You look a bit down.
Is something on your mind?
Huh?
"Date"?
No, this was...
Oh, I get it.
Are you trying to write a date scene?
Y-Yeah.
I have no experience in that field,
so I hit a bit of a wall.
You should have told me!
I said I'd help you out, right?
Thanks.
But I'll figure this one out myself.
Want to give it a try, with me?
Give what a try?
A date.
I actually said yes.
Me and Serizawa, on a date?
Nope. No way.
Jeez, I hope I don't look weird.
Maybe I should've bought a new outfit.
Not that I even have one fashionable fit.
Suzuki.
His casual clothes are blinding!
Sorry, did I keep you waiting?
Never mind.
- Not happening.
- Where are you going?
Sorry, it's just...
You look too cool.
Aw, thanks for the compliment.
Of course I'd dress my best today.
I've got a date with you.
A date...
Come on, let's go.
Where?
Somewhere I know you'll love.
No way...
This is where HaseFuka had their first date
in "Stars in the Deep Sea"!
Why?
Why not do a drama pilgrimage on our date?
You're the best, Serizawa.
This is amazing!
I wish I brought my acrylic standees...
I thought you'd say that.
HaseFuka standees?
Genius.
You're too perfect.
Right?
Here.
Hasegawa...
Right, pictures.
Let's take plenty.
Ready?
Say cheese.
Another one?
Sounds good.
Say cheese.
There are so many fish.
You're right.
I think those are char.
- Char?
- Yeah.
Know what scene happens here?
Isn't this where HaseFuka held hands?
Bingo.
Here.
Huh?
This is a date, isn't it?
But we're only doing it for research.
Exactly.
So, let's really go through
the motions of a date.
Not like that. Like this.
Come on.
Woah.
My heart's pounding...
Cute!
There's a whole school in there.
What's this fish called?
- A piranha.
- That's definitely wrong.
They're so cute...
Small, too.
Agreed.
There's a smaller one over there!
I've heard about these.
Can I give it a try?
Sure. Stick your hand in.
Am I allowed to?
Yeah. Go for it.
They're already crowding!
Wait, pause!
There are way too many of them!
Does this mean...
Guess you had tons of dead skin built up.
That's embarrassing.
I feel exposed...
- Let me see your hand.
- Okay.
A capybara!
Oh yeah, I see its face.
It's poking its nose out.
There's a turtle, too!
I see it.
Cute.
HaseFuka rang this bell.
Let's give it a try, too.
Ready?
Louder than I thought.
- There's so much.
- I'd like to get something.
Me too.
That's cute.
Let's buy a matching pair.
We're acting like a real couple.
Here you are.
Enjoy your drinks!
Isn't that guy good-looking?
You're right. Maybe he's a model.
Go ask him.
No way! I'm not pretty enough
to be seen with him.
Girl, you're too self-conscious.
Hey, I'm back.
Do you want the Blue Hawaiian
or the Cream Soda?
Thanks.
I'm fine with either.
Then here.
That's good. Try it.
Sure.
Thanks.
It tastes good.
Is everything okay?
Fine.
I just feel bad.
Huh?
I mean, I'm no match for you.
What?
I don't think I'm following.
Don't you get it?
You're good-looking,
and you know how to dress yourself.
But me?
I'm so unstylish, I'm doing you a disservice.
You're not giving yourself enough credit.
Huh?
Who cares about what others think?
I like your style.
I like the outfit and your hair.
I like your face and personality, too.
You're being a bit too generous there.
I also like how you're a dedicated writer.
See? Even now, you're taking notes.
But I've never finished a single story.
I only take notes because
I have a bad memory, too.
I'm not smart, nor athletic.
It takes me double the time to accomplish
what others can do easily.
Suzuki.
Don't focus on the expectations of others.
Accept the fact that I think you're awesome.
You're adorable, Suzuki.
You're at the top of my list
of people I want at my side.
Got it?
All right, good boy.
Let me go.
Stop it!
So?
Think you can write a date scene now?
Yeah. Thanks for helping me out today.
Huh? Isn't this...
You finally noticed.
I knew it. This is where HaseFuka kiss!
Bingo.
Wow...
Are you going to write a kiss scene?
Yeah. I plan to close out the date with one.
I see. How will it play out?
Uh, well...
I think I'll have the top
stop the bottom from going home
by asking for a kiss.
And then...
That's not bad.
But how about something more natural?
"Natural"?
Face me.
First, they'll happen to glance
at each other.
Then, they'll gaze into each other's eyes.
Slowly, but surely,
their hearts will become one.
And then, before they realize
what's happening...
So? Did you get all that?
Suzuki?
Oh no.
I can't take this anymore.
Suzuki. Look at me.
I guess it's true.
I...
I like Serizawa after all.
Forget it, forget it, forget it.
Forget it!
- Wh-What?
- Nothing.
Just wanted to say I had fun yesterday.
As if I could forget.